CONNOR J. HEINRICH

MANAGEMENT CONSULTANT AND SALES PROFESSIONAL

Seasoned Consultant and Sales Professional. Possesses 8 years of continued success in the software and information technology industry. Intensely focused on identifying customer problems and providing innovative application and data solutions. Education and experience fueled passion for the US Public Sector and modernizing enterprise technology.

- ✓ Agile Project Management
- ✓ Requirements Gathering and Analysis
- ✓ Change Management
- ✓ Data Analysis
- ✓ Data Visualization
- ✓ Stakeholder Engagement
- ✓ Product Development

- ✓ Business Development
- ✓ Market Research
- ✓ Public Speaking
- ✓ Technical Requirements Documentation
- ✓ Customer Service
- ✓ Strategic Planning
- ✓ Business Intelligence

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

JDM SOMA LLC | Washington, D.C.

Business and Systems Analyst, August 2016 to February 2018

IT Project Management and Data Analytics for the U.S. General Services Administration. Supporting projects at both the Public Buildings Service's Office of Acquisition Management and the Federal Acquisition Service's Transactional Data Reporting Program

Key Contributions:

- Team lead for 12 developers and designers modernizing the General Services Administration's web technologies
- Managed acquisition reporting on \$3 billion in annual sales transactional data for the Federal Acquisition Service
- Designed and implemented a new Tableau Data Analytics program for over 1,200 users to drive efficiencies in the acquisition community and provide financial accounting visibility for the Public Building Service
- Gathered, documented and prioritized hundreds of unique business requirements via numerous conference calls, interviews, emails and user surveys to support the client's IT acquisition system development priorities
- Executed a system communications plan for information sharing and user community engagement and education

BLOOMBERG L.P. | Washington, D.C.

Sales Representative, April 2013 to August 2016

Customer Advocate, Proven Business Leader and Builder.

Key Contributions:

- Booked over \$1.3 million in subscriptions while growing my business to 225 clients
- 2015 Top Sales Performer: Recognized as a top Bloomberg Government sales contributor and selected to attend NYC leadership conference
- 2015 Innovation Hackathon Winner: Led team to create a new client on-boarding automation method that is now in production across the Bloomberg Government vertical
- Consulted clients on corporate government affairs strategy and federal business best practices
- Developed multiple client segments and relationships, closed marquee accounts and delivered consistent results in a difficult startup sales environment

BLOOMBERG L.P. | Washington, D.C.

Congressional and Non-Profit Account Manager, February 2011 to April 2013

Conducted Door-to-Door Business Development on Capitol Hill. Gained the trust of hundreds of the nation's policymakers.

Key Contributions:

- Managed 27 Congressional and 23 non-profit accounts, delivering specialized training and custom news and data analytics reports for 301 customers
- Prospected for new business, set sales appointments, presented web platform and acquired 40 new accounts and \$600,000 with Congressional sales team partner
- Captured 1/4 of total House and Senate marketplace as part of a small team effort

BLOOMBERG L.P. | Washington, D.C.

Sales Operations Analyst, October 2010 to February 2011

Joined Bloomberg L.P.'s Bloomberg Government web start-up on the ground floor and quickly became invaluable.

Key Contributions:

- Provided remote and in-person software and hardware technical support for two sales teams; 12 people in total for computer, phone and software issues
- Navigated excel, CRM and internal systems to manage teams' calendars, mass mailings, expenses, room
 reservations, catering, travel arrangements and sales reports

U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES | Washington, D.C.

House Committee on Foreign Affairs Intern, August 2010 to September 2010

Completed highly competitive summer internship on Capitol Hill supporting U.S. Foreign Policy.

Key Contributions:

- Archived communications between Committee and various U.S. government agencies
- Researched and analyzed pending House and Senate legislation

EDUCATION

Dartmouth College | Hanover, N.H.

Bachelor of Arts, Government and Spanish Literature, 2010

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND INTERESTS

Scrum Alliance, ScrumMaster

Tableau Software, Inc.: Tableau Desktop 10 Qualified Associate

Skilled in SQL, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, JIRA, Agile Development, Ruby-on-Rails, Salesforce, MongoDB, GitHub, Bloomberg Professional Service, US Political Process, US Public Sector Contracting.

World Traveler. Bilingual. Outdoor Enthusiast. Avid Bicyclist.

AWARDS AND RECOGNITION

- 2015 Top Sales Performer, Bloomberg L.P. Web Verticals (January 2016)
- 2015 Innovation Hackathon Winner, Bloomberg Government (October 2015)
- DC Startup Weekend Winner, TechStars Startup Weekend (December 2011)